<FileDefinition version="2">
    <Description><![CDATA[
Defines measurements for products. 

This is the preferred structure for measurements of the `Product` entity.
Offers more measurement than what was previously support in the `Product` entity directly. 

Introduced in March 2022.
    ]]></Description>
    <Fields>
        <Field iskey="1">
            <Name>ProductCode</Name>
            <IsRequired>True</IsRequired>
            <Type>nvarchar</Type>
            <MaximumLength>150</MaximumLength>
        </Field>
        <Field iskey="1">
            <Name>MeasurementTypeID</Name>
            <IsRequired>True</IsRequired>
            <Type>tinyint</Type>
            <FixedValueList>
                <Value>1</Value>
                <Value>2</Value>
                <Value>3</Value>
                <Value>4</Value>
                <Value>5</Value>
                <Value>6</Value>
                <Value>7</Value>
                <Value>8</Value>
                <Value>9</Value>
                <Value>10</Value>
                <Value>11</Value>
                <Value>12</Value>
                <Value>13</Value>
            </FixedValueList>
            <Description><![CDATA[
Values supported by NatchOS:

- `1`: Base Unit - Unit in which the product is stored (inventory). Requires only the unit of measure. 
- `2`: Size - Measurement for a generic size/dimension of the product. Requires both the unit of measure and a value.
- `3`: Gross Weight - Measurement for the gross weight of the product. Requires both the unit of measure and a value.
- `4`: Net Weight - Measurement for the net weight of the product. Requires both the unit of measure and a value.
- `5`: Sales Unit - Unit in which the product is sold. Requires only the unit of measure. 
- `6`: Volume - Measurement for the volume of the product. Requires both the unit of measure and a value.
- `7`: Overpack Volume - Measurement for the volume of an overpack of the product. Requires both the unit of measure and a value.
- `8`: Overpack Weight - Measurement for the weight of an overpack of the product. Requires both the unit of measure and a value.
- `9`: Size Length - Measurement for the length of the product. Requires both the unit of measure and a value.
- `10`: Size Width - Measurement for the width of the product. Requires both the unit of measure and a value.
- `11`: Size Height - Measurement for the height of the product. Requires both the unit of measure and a value.
- `12`: Overpack Unit - Unit of one overpack. Requires only the unit of measure.
- `13`: Items per Sales Unit - Describes how many items are contained in a single sales unit. Requires both the unit of measure and a value. (I.e. Number of blisters in one package. Product is sold per package.)
    ]]></Description>
        </Field>
        <Field>
            <Name>UnitOfMeasureCode</Name>
            <IsRequired>True</IsRequired>
            <Type>nvarchar</Type>
            <MaximumLength>150</MaximumLength>
            <Description><![CDATA[
The code of the unit of measure.
    ]]></Description>
        </Field>
        <Field>
            <Name>Amount</Name>
            <Type>decimal</Type>
            <Precision>19</Precision>
            <Scale>6</Scale>
            <AltHeaderNames>
                <Value>Value</Value>
            </AltHeaderNames>
            <Description><![CDATA[
The value for the measurement. This is required for some measurement types.
    ]]></Description>
        </Field>
        <Field builtintype="Action"/>
    </Fields>
</FileDefinition>
